<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infor_popups>
<infor>
<id-element>current-age</id-element>
<name>current-age</name>
<message><![CDATA[<p><b><font color='#06038d'>Current age</font></b></p>
<p>The calculation will be based on complete years from the current date to the same date in your retirement year.</p>
<p>If you are using this modeller when it is close to your next birthday, you may wish to use your current age + 1.</p>]]></message>
</infor>
<infor>
<id-element>gender</id-element>
<name>gender</name>
<message><![CDATA[<p><b><font color='#06038d'>Gender</font></b></p>
<p>One of the factors that is used to calculate your annuity rate is an estimation of your expected mortality – how long you are likely to live.</p>]]></message>
</infor>
<infor>
<id-element>current-salary</id-element>
<name>current-salary</name>
<message><![CDATA[<p><b><font color='#06038d'>Annual salary</font></b></p>
<p>Enter your gross salary (before deductions).</p>]]></message>
</infor>
<infor>
<id-element>age-retirement</id-element>
<name>age-retirement</name>
<message><![CDATA[<p><b><font color='#06038d'>Retirement age</font></b></p>
<p>The age at which you choose to start to draw money from your pension has a significant impact on the amount of money you will receive. If you retire early, there will be less money in your pension pot and you will receive a smaller pension.
<p>This calculator does not include State Pension.</p>]]></message>
</infor>
<infor>
<id-element>target-pension</id-element>
<name>target-pension</name>
<message><![CDATA[<p><b><font color='#06038d'>Target income</font></b></p>
<p>Enter the annual income amount that you  think you will need to maintain your desired lifestyle when you retire.</p>]]></message>
</infor>
<infor>
<id-element>tax-free-cash</id-element>
<name>tax-free-cash</name>
<message><![CDATA[<p><b><font color='#06038d'>Tax free cash</font></b></p>
<p>You can take up to 25% of your pension pot as a tax free lump sum.</p>
<p>This is capped at 25% of the current LTA (Lifetime  Allowance) determined by the Government. Anything above that will be taxed at your normal rate.</p>
<p>If your pension pot exceeds the current LTA value, your cash lump sum will be capped accordingly in this calculator.</p>]]></message>
</infor>
</infor_popups>